materials we'll be using a glue scissors
我们将使用胶剪刀的材料
和购物车以及所有这些的详细信息
materials we'll be using a glue scissors
and cart and details about all these
资料在
入门教程，所以额外的折痕
and cart and details about all these
materials is explained more fully in the
这是添加的基本默认设置
产生更多两个平面的折痕
materials is explained more fully in the
introductory tutorial so extra creases
可以扩展和沟壑
可以内置到这是一个
introductory tutorial so extra creases
this is a basic default with added
平行折叠我们又有更多
产生另一个沟壑的折痕
this is a basic default with added
creases that create two more planes
你可以建立也创造额外的
可以扩展这一架飞机
creases that create two more planes
which can be built extended and a gully
再次，这是基本的V形折叠
这种情况下，额外的折痕
which can be built extended and a gully
which can be built into this one is a
而不是用来创造沟壑般的
在这一节中，他们已经缩小到
which can be built into this one is a
parallel fold again we've got extra
创建两个标签，然后将其解除
另一个孔对的飞机
parallel fold again we've got extra
creases which create another gully that
造成另一个您可以想到的沟壑
的基础上，让我们开始
creases which create another gully that
you can build into also creates extra
建立其中之一
所以我们把一张底纸对折
you can build into also creates extra
planes that can be extended this one
无需衡量无需评分
这类卡是160 GSM
planes that can be extended this one
again this is a basic V folds and in
影印卡，所以很容易
折起来真的很折
again this is a basic V folds and in
this case the the extra creases rather
彻底将其折叠几下
次卷曲它一次又一次
this case the the extra creases rather
than being used to create the gully like
您的基础表将需要
弹出另一张卡片
than being used to create the gully like
in this one they've been trimmed down to
所以我们只拿了三分之一
卡只是通过眼睛只是大致
in this one they've been trimmed down to
create two tabs and that's lifting it
折卡折半折
真的很彻底，然后重新折起你
create two tabs and that's lifting it
another hole pair of planes which again
希望两个折痕成一个角度出现
所以我们开始这是折线
another hole pair of planes which again
creates another gully that you can think
从底座上方约半英寸开始
折成一定角度将其折起
creates another gully that you can think
of build on so let's just start by
好吧，把它自己折起来
你可以切掉那个角
of build on so let's just start by
building one of these
使几个标签修剪那些
角落只是为了整洁，所以在这里我们
so we take a base sheet fold it in half
具有基本的基本V型折叠弹出形状
折痕全部向下
no need to measure no need to score with
指向箭头，您现在可以选择
我们将添加两个折痕
no need to measure no need to score with
this type of card this is 160 GSM
基本上，他们大致遵循
你可以做到这一点的线
this type of card this is 160 GSM
photocopy card so it's really easy to
绝对平行，或者您可以将其设为
下降得更陡一些
photocopy card so it's really easy to
fold just crease it really really
是原始的折痕，所以我们将其折叠
很好地将其折叠起来
fold just crease it really really
thoroughly fold it back on itself a few
打开它，现在它会折起来
下
thoroughly fold it back on itself a few
times crimp it again and again that's
所以当我们将其粘贴到页面上时
这就是我们要得到的
times crimp it again and again that's
your base sheet that would take a
我们知道v40可以玩
页面上片的角度为
your base sheet that would take a
another piece of card to make the pop-up
当你变得比你更紧
Guddi，您已经创造了额外的
so we just take about a third of the
麻袋褶皱点回落至低点或
你走得更宽，沟壑抬起，所以你
so we just take about a third of the
card just just by eye just roughly the
可以在这些折角上玩
它会影响整体形状
card just just by eye just roughly the
folded card fold it in half crease it
我们先将其粘贴下来
我再剪一点
folded card fold it in half crease it
really thoroughly and then refold you
更加锐利，因此它们不会重叠在
脊椎，所以我们在
really thoroughly and then refold you
want two creases coming up at an angle
弹出中心之间的角度
折痕和粘合上的折痕
want two creases coming up at an angle
so we start this is the folded line
选项卡，他们双方都是相同的，
现在我们要在基础上对称
so we start this is the folded line
start about half an inch above the base
是v形折叠，这将向下折叠
通孔指向的方向
start about half an inch above the base
fold it up at an angle crease it really
这将像这样折叠下来以获得
对称性我们只是粘在一侧
fold it up at an angle crease it really
well and fold it back on itself
第一
在页面顶部附近
you can cut cut that corner out cut this
确保中央中央折痕
弹出窗口与沟槽对齐
you can cut cut that corner out cut this
to make a couple of tabs trim off those
把它粘在一边
向下稳稳地移动，我可以折叠
to make a couple of tabs trim off those
corners just for neatness and so here we
整件进入关闭位置
将胶水放在另一个标签上涂抹胶水
corners just for neatness and so here we
have the basic basic v-fold pop-up shape
直到折痕，然后
折叠页面关闭
have the basic basic v-fold pop-up shape
the the creases all make a downward
所以在这里我们有这个V折
现在在顶部创建了一个额外的后卫
the the creases all make a downward
pointing arrow now you've got a choice
您可以内置或添加
你可能只是选择采取一些奇怪的
pointing arrow now you've got a choice
we're going to add two more creases
这样的卡，你可以
像这样或这样粘贴
we're going to add two more creases
basically they they roughly follow the
你知道我可以折叠，你可以胶水
把它粘到沟渠的任何地方
basically they they roughly follow the
the line of that one you can make it
你喜欢，你开始真正地
用这种形状雕刻，所以我就用胶水
the line of that one you can make it
absolutely parallel or you can make it a
那一个
所以把它放进去，当你用
absolutely parallel or you can make it a
bit coming down a bit more steeply this
每次您使用弹出窗口进行构建
在底座上加一块，然后按一下
bit coming down a bit more steeply this
is the original fold so we fold it over
坚定地，这样一步一步就可以
确保整个结构健全
is the original fold so we fold it over
crease it well fold it back on itself
是的，但它运作正常
在电话工作，但
open it up and now this will fold back
胶正在工作，在这种情况下
我们不妨添加另一个
open it up and now this will fold back
down
另外一点他们平行折叠在顶部
这样，您就可以分散另一个
down
so when we stick this onto the page this
一张卡片将其对折添加一半
几个选项卡修剪它们这将
so when we stick this onto the page this
is what we're going to get and again as
适应我们刚刚提到的沟壑
创建，所以她将适合
is what we're going to get and again as
we know v40 can play with the play with
这样，您只需在上面涂一点胶
一个标签将其涂抹到边缘一点
we know v40 can play with the play with
the angle of the piece on the page as
有点，这是平行的，所以
一切都必须与
the angle of the piece on the page as
you as you make it tighter than the
沟渠中的折痕将其固定到位
将胶水放在另一个标签上涂抹胶水
you as you make it tighter than the
Guddi that you've created the extra
折叠整块，以便找到
它自然的自然黏附位置
Guddi that you've created the extra
gunny folds points back down low or as
这是基本的V折
增加折痕，然后折起
gunny folds points back down low or as
you go wider the gully lifts up so you
另外两架飞机
平行折叠卡在其顶部
you go wider the gully lifts up so you
can play with the angles on these folds
所以你可以看看这个
并弹出
can play with the angles on these folds
and it it affects the overall shape so
从中弹出的基础
你可以这样看
and it it affects the overall shape so
we'll start by just gluing this down
基本表作为背景
从我们所有的弹出窗口
we'll start by just gluing this down
I'll just cut these a bit more a little
在这里制成的是一个抽象的形状
玩雕塑
I'll just cut these a bit more a little
sharper so they don't overlap on the
再一次，你实际上已经从
原始v折
sharper so they don't overlap on the
spine and so we've got symmetry on the
那是你现在实际拥有的两架飞机
有六架飞机，所以这些都可以
spine and so we've got symmetry on the
pop-up the angles between the central
扩展，您可以脱颖而出
一个你可以从第二个沟壑中冒出来
pop-up the angles between the central
crease and the creases on the gluing
您可以在哪里出现
平行折叠这一切都只是抽象
crease and the creases on the gluing
tabs they're both the same each side and
在这一点上，只是使用
你的想象力看到你想要去的地方
tabs they're both the same each side and
now we want symmetry on on the base and
换种方式，你可以玩这个
而不是创建两个平面
now we want symmetry on on the base and
being a v-fold this will fold down in
用沟渠可以制作襟翼
我会选一个给你看
being a v-fold this will fold down in
the direction that the vias pointing so
如何工作需要折纸
折成一半真的很好
the direction that the vias pointing so
this will fold down like this so to get
将折痕折回去
自己一次又一次地压着他们
this will fold down like this so to get
the symmetry we just just glue one side
这是您的基础，现在我们将建立
到这里很冷所以
the symmetry we just just glue one side
first
拿张卡片不计
随便切一下就知道了
up near the up near the top of the page
将您的尺寸折成半折痕
很好地将其折回自身
up near the up near the top of the page
make sure the central central crease on
再次下降，然后我们将
基本的V折，所以这是折线
make sure the central central crease on
the pop-up is
从折起大约半英寸开始
远离远处倾斜一个角度
the pop-up is
glue it down so that's one side glued
从中央折起再折回去
本身，你打开它
glue it down so that's one side glued
down firmly moving nicely I can fold the
您已经具备基本的V型折叠设计
你有所有的折痕
down firmly moving nicely I can fold the
whole piece into its closed position and
向下箭头，所以现在我们将
只需修剪一下即可制作用于
whole piece into its closed position and
put glue on the other tab smear the glue
V形饰边更加锋利，因此
它不会重叠和脊椎，所以这是
put glue on the other tab smear the glue
to the the up to the crease and then
您的基本V折件现在让我们制作一个
顶部的手机
to the the up to the crease and then
fold the page shut
所以这次来这样
我或多或少与
so here here we have this this V fold
与原始的，你可以进来
或多或少的任何角度
so here here we have this this V fold
now has an extra guard created on top
你进来会影响形状
你做的，但是没有权利
now has an extra guard created on top
which you can build into or you can add
在这种情况下没有错，我想要
顶部略窄，所以我要
which you can build into or you can add
on you may just choose to take some odd
从角落修剪下来
我要这样切
on you may just choose to take some odd
piece of card like this and you can just
我将把它们修剪成另外两个
标签，所以现在我们有了标签的V形折叠
piece of card like this and you can just
stick it on like this or like this or
在顶部，所以我们对折
他们指向的方向，所以我们
stick it on like this or like this or
you know I can fold it and you can glue
希望它在您的顶部附近
页面我们有对称性，所以两个
you know I can fold it and you can glue
that glue that into the gulley anywhere
中央折痕两侧的角度
在弹出窗口上都一样
that glue that into the gulley anywhere
you like and you're starting to actually
现在我们要在页面上对称，因此
胶水只是将胶水放在一个标签上
you like and you're starting to actually
sculpt with this shape so I'll just glue
从开始就开始工作
想要一个非常尖锐的形状或更宽的形状
sculpt with this shape so I'll just glue
that one in
我大约要在45度左右行驶，
再次无所谓，只取决于
so put it in and as you build with as
取决于您要创建什么形状
现在将胶水放在另一个标签上
so put it in and as you build with as
you build with pop-ups every time you
并关闭它，所以在这里我们有一个
V形折叠，顶部有一对标签
you build with pop-ups every time you
add a piece close the base and press it
你可以建立这个，所以你采取
另一块对折
add a piece close the base and press it
firmly so as you go step by step you're
我实际上可能更喜欢它，所以
现在我把它折成两半
firmly so as you go step by step you're
sure that the whole structure is sound
这是我们制作的
以前是因为你在工作
sure that the whole structure is sound
that it's but it's working that it fits
有沟壑，你只能使这些
突出显示所产生的角度
that it's but it's working that it fits
in that the phones work but the that the
在这种情况下，因为你已经
有标签，您实际上可以看到纱丽
in that the phones work but the that the
gluing is working and this in this case
周围，​​所以您可以选择拥有它
真的非常陡峭，或者您可以选择
gluing is working and this in this case
we might as well just add another
拥有它甚至可以指向下方
这样，标签和将坚持
we might as well just add another
another little them parallel fold on top
在那里，所以你可以看到抱歉
围绕并决定您想要的形状
another little them parallel fold on top
of that so you can scatter just another
然后在这种情况下，你不会粘一个
选项卡，然后另一个放胶
of that so you can scatter just another
piece of card fold it in half add a
同时在两个标签上
两个标签上的胶都涂抹到
piece of card fold it in half add a
couple of tabs trim them this is going
边缘
真的要在什么角度上
couple of tabs trim them this is going
to fit into that gully that we've just
我或多或少会水平
你只要把整块都折下来
to fit into that gully that we've just
created so she's going to fit in like
那里我们有它，再次你可以
可以以此为基础
created so she's going to fit in like
this so you just put a bit of glue on on
看着它，你可能会喜欢
看起来像你甚至
this so you just put a bit of glue on on
one tab smear it to the edges a little
喜欢看那样的样子
由你决定，你又一次知道
one tab smear it to the edges a little
bit this is a parallel fold so it's got
你实际上还有另一个沟壑
不是很好，不是很深，但是
bit this is a parallel fold so it's got
everything's got to be parallel with the
你可以建立到这个或再次你可以
刚开始你就知道要坚持下去
everything's got to be parallel with the
crease in the gully stick it into place
只是在屁股上的碎片
周围会形成有趣的形状
crease in the gully stick it into place
put glue on the other tab smear the glue
这就是我要展示的全部
你在做事方面
put glue on the other tab smear the glue
fold the whole piece shut so it finds
很好，这是一样的
想法，但这是一个v-fold
fold the whole piece shut so it finds
its natural natural sticking position so
红色V形提起蓝鸟，所以
这就像我们刚刚制作的作品
its natural natural sticking position so
here it is it's a basic V fold with
我现在向您展示一些示例
书中的额外折痕
here it is it's a basic V fold with
added creases which is then lifting up
所以这是跳科夫斯基的晚餐时间
这是冷杉，这只是一个
added creases which is then lifting up
two more planes which has then got a
基本弹出窗口，这是v形折叠
一个减少，所以在这里你可以看到
two more planes which has then got a
parallel fold stuck into the top of it
只是V折，整个事情就
关闭，然后添加折痕
parallel fold stuck into the top of it
so you can you can look at this either
你又多了两个飞机
大猩猩也一样
so you can you can look at this either
with the pop-up the base sheet of the
V形折叠可关闭增加的折痕
制作它，您可以在弹出时弹出
with the pop-up the base sheet of the
base with the pop-up rising from it or
到更多飞机和更有趣
雕塑形状再次相同
base with the pop-up rising from it or
you can look at it like this so this is
再次在这里我想要的另一本书
告诉你这是一些怪物群岛
you can look at it like this so this is
the base sheet as a background did the
怪物岛罗恩·范德米尔和这
点差这是基本的直角
the base sheet as a background did the
pop-up coming forward from it all we've
默认值，但在顶部已添加
创建此尺寸的折痕
pop-up coming forward from it all we've
made here is an abstract shape it's just
这只是你可以把它折叠下来
将其折平，但添加这些
made here is an abstract shape it's just
playing playing with the sculpture
他创造了更多的折痕
顶部有趣的雕塑形状
playing playing with the sculpture
and again now you've actually from the
弹出窗口，然后这个是这个
罗恩·范德·梅尔的咆哮狮子故事
and again now you've actually from the
original v-fold
这是一个平行故障
有额外的折痕，所以如果我们拉这个
original v-fold
that was two planes you've now actually
直，所以你可以看到这只是一个
非常大的平行折叠整体
that was two planes you've now actually
got six planes and so any of these can
单单今年秋天平，并通过添加
这些额外的折痕，他是他雕刻的
got six planes and so any of these can
be extended you can come up off the blue
整个形状，并使其成为一个真正的
坚固的3D形状，而不只是一种
be extended you can come up off the blue
one you can come up off the second gully
空心帐篷，然后我想
告诉你这是MP的机器人，
one you can come up off the second gully
where you can come up come off the of
科夫斯基和这本书中的最后一篇
这是火箭从云层升起吗
where you can come up come off the of
the parallel fold this all just abstract
云是基本的平行褶皱，
火箭这是v字形的腰带
the parallel fold this all just abstract
at this point and it's just yeah use
所以这是v形折叠
产生这种沟壑的折痕和
at this point and it's just yeah use
your imagination see where you want to
火箭是内置的平行折叠
火箭的沟壑和鼻子
your imagination see where you want to
go the other way you can play with this
我将向您展示的泥巴改良
另一个另一个教程，所以
go the other way you can play with this
is that rather than creating two planes
我在此谈论的一切
这本书涵盖了教程
is that rather than creating two planes
with a gully you can create flaps so
弹出式设计和纸张力学